// English Grammer
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "She ______ me to go to school.",
    answer: "told",
    options: [
      "said",
      "told",
      "suggested",
      "made"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The best way to learn a language is ______ a little every day.",
    answer: "by speaking",
    options: [
      "speak",
      "in speaking",
      "to speaking",
      "by speaking"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "He told me that he ______ in Spain the previous year.",
    answer: "had been working",
    options: [
      "has been working",
      "had been working",
      "has worked",
      "had been worked"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "She has been ______ of murdering her husband.",
    answer: "accused",
    options: [
      "charged",
      "arrested",
      "accused",
      "blames"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Would you mind ______ the window?",
    answer: "closing",
    options: [
      "closing",
      "close",
      "to close",
      "closed"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "He's interested ______ learning Spanish",
    answer: "in",
    options: [
      "on",
      "to",
      "in",
      "for"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Tim ______ work tomorrow.",
    answer: "isn't going to",
    options: [
      "isn't going",
      "isn't",
      "isn't going to",
      "isn't to"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The doctor gave me a ______ for some medicine yesterday.",
    answer: "prescription",
    options: [
      "note",
      "receipt",
      "prescription",
      "recipe"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Can you tell me when ______ ?",
    answer: "the train leaves",
    options: [
      "does the train leave",
      "the train leaves",
      "leave the train",
      "does leave the train"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "There aren't ______ people here.",
    answer: "many",
    options: [
      "much",
      "many",
      "a lot",
      "some"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "His office is on the second ______ of the building.",
    answer: "floor",
    options: [
      "floor",
      "level",
      "ground",
      "stage"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "If only I ______ richer.",
    answer: "were",
    options: [
      "am",
      "would be",
      "were",
      "will be"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "You aren't allowed to use your mobile so ______.",
    answer: "there's no point in leaving it on",
    options: [
      "it's no point in leaving it on",
      "it's no point to leave it on",
      "there's no point to leave it on",
      "there's no point in leaving it on"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 14,
    question: "We arrived ______ England two days ago.",
    answer: "in",
    options: [
      "to",
      "on",
      "in",
      "at"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "They have put speed bumps on the road to ______ accidents.",
    answer: "prevent",
    options: [
      "avoid",
      "prevent",
      "forbid",
      "prohibit"
    ]
  },
];